// src/questions.js
export const questions = [
  {
    prompt: "The Renaissance began in which country in the 14th century?",
    choices: ["Germany", "England", "France", "Italy"],
    answerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    prompt: "Who wrote The Handmaid's Tale?",
    choices: ["Margaret Atwood", "Joan Didion", "Virginia Woolf", "Jane Austen"],
    answerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    prompt: "What's the main ingredient in tofu?",
    choices: ["Peas", "Soybean", "Mozzarella", "Cashews"],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    prompt: "When is Kuromi's birthday?",
    choices: ["Nov 10th", "March 23rd", "Oct 31st", "July 4th"],
    answerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which famous musician was nicknamed Satchmo?",
    choices: ["Louis Armstrong", "Sarah Vaughan", "Nina Simone", "Peggy Lee"],
    answerIndex: 0,
  },
  {
    prompt: "What does the Tinman wish for in The Wizard of Oz?",
    choices: ["Brain", "Heart", "Courage", "Power"],
    answerIndex: 1,
  },
  {
    prompt: "Which Pokemon did Ash have to say goodbye to?",
    choices: ["Froslass", "Drampa", "Butterfree", "Mimikyu"],
    answerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    prompt: "Charles Darwin formulated his Theory of Evolution while observing which animal?",
    choices: ["Turtle", "Monkey", "Crocodile", "Finch"],
    answerIndex: 3,
  },
  {
    prompt: "In the nursery rhyme, what does the itsy bitsy spider do?",
    choices: ["Fell From A Great Wall", "Caught An Ant In Its Web", "Climb Up The Water Spout", "Sleep"],
    answerIndex: 2,
  },
  {
    prompt: "Bourgeoisie is a term used to describe?",
    choices: ["Marinated Meat", "Bungee Jumping", "The Middle Class", "Fossils"],
    answerIndex: 2,
  },
];